Not enough of us want to admit that those people that we revere and that we pedestal
would not revere and pedestal some of the individuals that some of you all revere and
pedestal because they understand that when it comes to aligning with certain ideologies,
it is counterintuitive to any level of equality.
So as much as some of you all want to simply stand on, well, Kamala Harris is Black, it
is very reasonable to say she was the only option I felt I could vote for.
However, it is unreasonable to suggest that she is anything counter to the system that
is holding liberation back.
That system has been in place long before her.
She has simply capitulated to it and is a part of this establishment and she continues
to perpetuate it.
She does, many other Black politicians, Black executives, Black celebrities, they all participate
in this practice.
So when you see folks like myself calling attention to them, they are figures of prominence that
have a platform that they could use to shift culture, to shift mindsets, to enable the people
to shift their own futures.
And instead, they use that platform to shift dollars towards themselves without doing anything
to challenge the very system that has been in place before them and that they are now aligning
themselves with.
To cut to the chase, Malcolm X and Martin Luther King are not supporters of liberals.
And anyone thinking they would be because those liberals are Black, I think you'd find differently
if you read their work.
In recent years, I've come to see that these are often the people who stand in the way
of progress because they are committed only in a lukewarm manner.
And every time you move to try to solve the problem, they will respond by saying, you're
moving too fast, you ought to cool off, you should put on brakes.
And they end up more devoted to order than to justice.
And spoiler alert, then she goes on to say that it's outrageous what's being done to
Palestinians without acknowledging her role in any of that.
And one more thing, Dr. Martin Luther King Jr., Malcolm X, June Jordan, Alice Walker, Tony
Morrison, Fannie Lou Hamer, Diane Nash, Ella Baker, we're all private citizens.
Support a real one.